invesp.com 2016-05-08

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Invesp uses and protects any information that you give Invesp when you use this website or register to use any of the websites or services operated by Invesp.

Invesp is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information, which may identify you and which you provide to Invesp when using our website or services will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Invesp may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1/1/2011.

## What we collect

When you register for the services, we ask you for information such as name, email, password, company name, website address and contact information.

When you login to the website, we track the IP address, browser information (Type, language, etc), date of your requests.

When you send email to Invesp, we keep record of the emails to process your requests. 

When you use our support system, we store your request information to process your requests.

If you install Invesp testing code on your website, we do NOT store any data to personally identify any your website visitors. The Invesp testing code will collect and store statistics about the usage of your website. Invesp will not share your website statistics without your consent. Invesp only processes personal information for the purpose of providing, improving, ensuring the delivery of, and developing new services to users.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information. Such information does not identify you individually.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have clicked on these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
